My name is Nthabeleng Paulette - 26 years old, from Lesotho.
Who are the people sitting next to you?
My aunt and uncle.
I'm a student, I still haven't completed.
What are you studying?
Property studies, valuation and quantity surveying,
at Namibian University of Science and Technology.
I have a connective tissue disorder called, ehlers-danlos syndrome,
which means that I have complications with all of my connective tissues;
all the organs, joints and tissues in my body can fail at any given time.
All my joints get dislocated.
My heart, liver, kidneys, bladder and muscles cannot work.
I can’t really walk sometimes because I get paralyzed at times.
Even my eyes dislocate, so I can’t see well; studying for me is very hard.
I have been out of school many times because of these attacks.
I haven’t finished school, even though I have been studying for over seven years.
I can’t do things that others can do – I can’t stand for long or walk.
I am aided with a wheelchair at times; sometimes I need arm, leg, back or shoulder guards.
Three to four of my joints get dislocated every day.
My breathing is also bad.
I have seizures frequently but it is not epilepsy.
My lungs are very weak, they cannot compress air so, I cannot breathe very well;
I have shortness of breath.
I cannot sing or dance for long; I cannot do any activity or run.
I have to walk and hold onto something, if I am walking but most of the time I just sit.
I have had this condition for close to 14 years.
I have visited almost every doctor in South Africa.
I have been to Lesotho, Botswana, I even visited doctors in Austria
and Germany but nobody could help, as nobody understood what I had.
I see therapists every day -
I have a bi-connectisist, a chiropractor and a physiotherapist who help me on a daily basis.
I do hydro-therapy to help my muscles but it doesn’t really help.
If I don’t do these things, I can’t do anything by myself.
Doctors have no solution for me except to keep my muscles as fit as possible.
But none of them can really help me because they do not know what causes these attacks.
I can have an attack where only the heart is having a problem.
Sometimes, everything doesn’t work at the same time.
So, the doctors and specialists don’t understand how to help me;
they help the symptoms, not the condition.
I have a lot of dislocations of the shoulder and elbow frequently.
I have to carry my brace with me to protect my arm in case it comes out.
If it is out, I have to relocate it and when it is out, it hurts.
The brace carries my shoulder.
I cannot carry heavy things at all; if I carry something, it will just pull out
and when I’m sleeping, it dislocates as well.
I have very flexible connective tissue, unlike normal people.
So, my joints get out of place easily.
As you can see, my finger bends right over – most people can’t do this.
I got to know about The SCOAN years ago from Emmanuel TV.
Years ago, my parents were watching and they called me to join them.
I have seen a lot of people being delivered, especially people with joint issues such as myself.
I have seen people who have not been walking, walk.
People who haven’t been able to use their limbs, use their limbs.
Therefore, I believe I can also be normal and walk like everybody else.
I believe Jesus will heal me and I will be normal; I will resume my studies
and I will be like everybody else and have a career.
I want to live life without pain because I am always in pain – 24/7.
I pray with you that the Lord Jesus Christ will use His able servant, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua,
to declare you free from these problems, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
HEALING TIME
Help me, Man of God; I have a genetic condition that makes my body non-functional.
I dislocate all the time.
Now, I dislocated about 5 times; my knee was out, my shoulder was out, and my jaws were out.
I can't go to school, I can't do any thing what everybody else does.
Everything doesn't work; my heart is weak, my lungs are weak.
Come on!
Healing In Jesus’ Name
Come on.
Alright, remove it.
Healing In Jesus’ Name
Stand up!
Just stand up and look at me!
What is your name?
Nthabeleng Ramoedi.
Walk majestically!
Thank You, Jesus - I'm healed!
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
Hello everybody, my name is Nthabeleng Ramoedi from Lesotho.
I came here because I had ehlers-danlos syndrome -
a connective tissue that affects every single muscle joint and organ in one's body.
I couldn't do anything everyone else could do.
My joints dislocated multiple times; they could pop out at any time, even when I was sleeping.
I was out of school half of the time, so I haven't even completed my studies,
even though I have been studying for 8 years.
I came here with a hope that I would be normal again, and thank God I'm walking,
which is actually not very normal for me to be walking.
Or alone talking, having a shortness of breath.
Usually, I wouldn't say more than 5 sentences; then, I wouldn't be able to breath.
I would need to have an asthma pump or something to help me breathe.
But, for the grace of God, since last week Sunday, when the man of God administered healing on me,
I became a different person, lighter and something...
OK, just before you explain further, we really want to understand;
we watched in the clip how you were explaining more about the severity of this condition.
Can you just once again, for the benefit of those present here and viewers -
can you just explain what was actually happening in your body, before you received prayer?
What was the challenge you were having; the pain you were having in your body - just describe to us more.
The pain I was having; think of walking every single day with about 10 breaks of every joint.
There was a constant pain that I had every single day.
Talking was massively painful because my jaws would pop out every time.
I couldn't eat anything, because if I ate, I couldn't digest - my intestines would twist around,
and I would look like pregnant half of the time.
Doctors couldn't help me whatsoever.
I couldn't see properly because my eyes would dislocate, so writing was a mission.
I wouldn't be able to read anything; even the Bible - I would hold the Bible for 2 minutes,
then things would start moving, and I couldn't see letters at all.
My life was constrained in a deep belittling state, constantly - 24/7.
I've probably been to more specialists than one human being should.
I know all sorts of...
I used to see cardiologists,
physiotherapists,
joints specialists, bones specialists, brain specialists, because nothing worked
and none of them could help me at all.
They would only help to stabilize me, so I would be able to at least receive medications.
But sometimes my body even rejected the medications they gave me.
So nothing actually worked.
The only thing that kept me going was that if they worked with my muscles,
it made them stronger, so I could take 10 steps instead of 3 steps.
Or, I could be able to breathe longer than I usually did by using a nebulizer or some sort of machine.
Especially in winters - for some weird reason, I would constantly be in the emergency room,
every other week or every other day.
How many diseases did the doctors actually diagnose in your body, as a result of this tissue disorder?
So far, I think I was in the range of between 60 and 70 conditions and diseases.
I could relate to almost everyone in the hospital who came through.
If you had diabetes, I had it,
if you had some sort of ulcer or intestinal issue, I had it,
if you had any sort of seizure, I've had it before.
So pretty much, I had every little problem you could think of.
We are listening to our sister; she said that medically, because of this very rare disorder she had,
the doctors actually diagnosed more than 60 to 70 different diseases in her system,
because of the abnormality she had as a result of this condition.
Just tell us, sister, you said that at any given time your joints would dislocate;
your shoulder, your knees, your arm -
just describe what would happen each time your shoulder or other part of your body would dislocate.
What would you have to do to try to fix the situation?
What was the kind of pain you would have at that moment?
Well, I don't know if anyone of you has broken a bone before, falling from a building or during an accident,
but it feels like you are crushing a bone every time something is dislocated.
There are two options: Most times, I would have to be rushed to the emergence room,
so the doctor could relocate a joint.
They always had to put me under heavy medication before they could put it back in,
because they were traumatising a lot of muscles around the joint, if it came out.
With time, because it became a part of my life, I learned how to put back some of the joints;
like the jaw one was a bit easier for me to put back,
or I would ask any other individual around me, and tell them how to move around,
by directing their hand, or something, so that they could put it back.
But normally, it was always an emergency to go to the doctor.
We are hearing what our sister is saying that on every day she would find a situation,
whereby a part of her body would actually dislocate,
and the pain she would experience would be as if she had broken a bone in her body.
If anyone has experienced that, you would know the magnitude of the pain involved.
She came to the point where she herself would physically start putting the parts of her body
that were dislocated back to the right position,
because she was so accustomed to the different parts of her body dislocating,
or, she would find someone nearby and instruct them how to actually put that part of her body back,
to the correct position, because of the nature of that problem.
You mean to say sister, this is how you have been living your life for many years, in that intense pain and agony?
Yes, that is exactly how I have been living.
For example, I think the worst kind of dislocation that I experienced is a rib cage coming completely out.
If anybody has had a fracture of a rib, or had it bruised for some reason, due to sports injury,
he would know that it is probably the worst bone to get fractured at any point.
It is massively...
It feels like you are dying, pretty much.
I don't know what death feels like, but I feel like that's probably the worst type of pain anybody can feel.
And the hip as well.
Anybody with a hip replacement - usually old people would sympathize because they understand how it feels,
but I felt all that agony pain at the early age of 12.
So, pretty much, I have been feeling pain through all my life,
which is why this is very weird - I have never felt like this before.
We are still going to come to how our sister received her healing,
but we are just asking these questions, so that our viewers around the world, and those present here
can know the power of God, that we are under, by the grace of God - here, in the arena of liberty.
Now, sister, you said that because of this constant pain,
just describe - were you able to live a normal kind of a childhood,
like for example with your going to school, or the kind of activities other young children would do?
How did this condition really affect you to separate you from the crowd,
in the sense that you couldn't do what others in school were doing?
I couldn't do sports for example, or go on tours if something were to happen at school.
I would always be conformed to a classroom.
Even in the classroom itself, I would always be...
Every week there was a mystery that an ambulance was going to come
and I would have to go to the emergency room.
So much that when there was an ambulance around the school,
people seeing me walking or sitting would say, "Oh, it wasn't you? We thought it was you again".
I was so accustomed to always being pulled out of school that it was a part of me.
I didn't do any activity, because if I tried to jump over something, I would break something,
if I tried to write something in class, I would write two sentences,
then my arm would dislocate, so it wouldn't really work.
Even exams; they were trying to figure out how to make me write exams,
without me actually having to be in pain.
Most of my final high-school exams, I wrote them with my left hand.
By the grace of God, I don't know how, I still passed anyway.
Sister, we also want you to describe; you said that it reached a point where you couldn't even sleep,
because of the severity of this pain.
Can you just describe what would happen to you in the night?
What was a normal night like for you because of this?
Most people probably know what insomnia is - think of it as being constant.
When doctors would do sleep-test on me to see my neurological balance,
one neurologist told me that it seems as if I haven't slept in over 3 years.
Because my brain is always working, the chemicals in the brain were never balanced, so I was never asleep.
I would close my eyes in the midst of hoping to sleep, but I would just toss and turn the whole time
or be up because my bladder was always full, even though I peed
like a teaspoon of pee, but I would always have to rush to the bathroom.
So, I never really slept.
Because of that, throughout the day you would be tired, in whatever you would do.
You would easily just find yourself sleeping off, because you hadn't actually slept in the night?
True.
Half of my classes I would have my head on the desk.
Some lecturers thought I was just an annoying child because I never really spoke about my condition.
In a classroom of 400 students - who cares?
You are just there to do your work and therefore you have to stand up,
but people would just be like, "Why do you always rest your head on the table?",
or "Why can't you sit up straight like everybody else?"
Because of my fracture on the back of my spine, it literally curved in, so I couldn't stand up straight;
in fact even standing straight like this was not a normal thing for me - I would have to slouch back,
because my spine couldn't stand up straight.
We saw in the interview - we can actually see on the board here;
there were some pictures that were displayed, showing you in some unusual positions.
Could you just describe to us again, for the benefit of our viewers,
why we are seeing these pictures, and what your body condition was like before?
For example, this particular picture shows that I was hyper flexible,
meaning that when your body stops at a certain fraction, mine "over-moved" - it was extensively bendy.
Most people with this condition don't pick it up until when they try to move, something pops out.
When you are a kid, it is not easy to detect; they just thought I was a flexible child -
maybe I was going to join the circus, or something.
But then, as I grew older, I was supposed to be stiffer, but it didn't get stiff at all.
It just got lax and lax.
I could fit in a box, if you wanted to put me in there.
There was nothing holding my joints in place, so things would just pop out all the time.
This particular picture shows that I was usually under some sort of machine constantly to help me breath,
because my breathing was really bad.
This is one of my best friends, from the past obviously, not anymore - my sling.
It would always have to be in one of my school bags, even if I left the house with no dislocation,
because chances were that the day would not end without something popping out.
And if I left it hanging, it would hurt longer.
This was to support so that nobody touched or bumped me by mistake,
not knowing that it hurt or went out.
These are my knee guards, different types.
The other one is metal-based, because there was always liquid transforming from my spine to my knee,
so my knee would just swell up with a lot of liquid.
They couldn't drain it because if you opened any part of my body, I would bleed non-stop.
So, operations were never advised, because every time I was opened, something was going to happen,
therefore I was just "bleed-dry".
In conclusion, this was a miserable way to live.
I couldn't go out, I have not done anything teenagers do;
I just read about it, or hear about it from my sisters; like they went out to a concert -
even a gospel concert, I've never done that.
Every time the weather changed from hot to cold, from evening to night, I reacted and got sick.
If I were to move out of the room with air conditioning, and it was hot outside, I would probably faint.
Viewers around the world, we have listened to our sister.
This is the severity of this very rare condition that she had when she came in.
Just tell us sister - how rare is this condition that you were having in your body?
Are you aware of how many people around the world have this kind of condition?
It's extensively rare.
Even in the countries where we think medicine is widely more exposed than down here in Africa,
only about 10% of the whole population is diagnosed.
And only 1 person in 100 000 might have it - that is how rare it is,
but no one knows what to do about it.
It takes years for most people to get diagnosed.
Even a doctor herself, who did research, only discovered in her fifties that she had this sickness,
and she was a practising doctor for more than 10 years.
We thank God that in the midst of this very extreme condition, God brought you to The SCOAN.
We saw on the clip earlier, when you cried out for prayer, as the man of God,
Prophet T.B. Joshua passed by, and he began to pray for you.
We just want you to describe to us, at that moment, can you just relive what happened,
as the Prophet began to pray for you?
When the Prophet came over, for some reason I couldn't talk for the first couple of seconds.
Then I don't know what happened afterwards.
I remember being on the floor and I was shaking uncontrollably - I don't know the reasons.
The next thing I heard was him telling me to look him in the eyes -
the eyes were a bit weary, so it took a while.
After I looked at him straight up and I was standing,
I felt some sort of relief; as if I became 10 times lighter than I usually am.
I almost fell over because I wasn't aware that I was that light.
Then I started walking and I started feeling no pain,
and I felt like, "What is going on here? This is not normal."
I was supposed to be taking my time up, but I was shaking like the wind was just blowing me.
It was some sense of relief and I just knew right there that everything that I had been through was over.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
You mean for the first time in your life, that you can recall, as you stood up at that moment,
you did not feel pain in your body?
Yes, which is still overwhelming really, to tell you the truth.
And ever since that prayer you received, can you just describe to us -
what are the incredible changes you've seen in your body, both physically and in terms of the pain.
Just describe to us what has happened after that prayer.
I can now do the head and shoulders thing.
The feet for example; my feet could never touch the ground fully;
but for the first time my toes and everything is on the shoe, which is very weird.
And I can walk, without feeling any pain.
Every time I walked; if you were close to me, you would hear my joints pop in and out making sound.
There is no more sound.
I can write properly now.
I wrote my name with one of the evangelists, and she was like, "It doesn't look like your handwriting".
Last week I wrote my name but it looked like a cat's scratch.
You couldn't make out whether the "E" wasn't an "A", or the "L" was a "T", but right now I can write.
For some reason I can read the Bible without my glasses even,
which I couldn't do previously, because my eyes would dislocate.
Wow, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
You said before that at any given time parts of your body would dislocate, pop out.
Ever since that prayer, just describe the changes you have seen in that area.
Ever since the prayer...
I would have dislocated my jaw by now of course, because I have been talking too much,
which is actually quite nice to talk.
Usually my hand would get stuck, if I was using my hands too much,
but no finger, no elbow, no hip, no neck, nothing has popped out ever since Sunday.
People who were with me before the man of God came to me would know that,
they were worried and trying to figure out how to put back my knee and my shoulder.
They were all actually very hysterical because they have never seen something like that before.
Some other person fainted for two minutes, I think.
You mean that on that Sunday before prayer, some parts of your body dislocated?
Five minutes before the man of God prayed for me, my joints had popped out.
As he came, there were already things being put back in place.
He moved and passed me and we were trying to fix one,
and then he moved again; when he came back, we were fixing the shoulder that came out,
but about 4 others had popped out within the 5 minutes space of time.
People of God, we can understand the nature of this miracle.
Our sister said that on that day, just minutes before Prophet T.B. Joshua even prayed for her,
5 different parts of her body dislocated.
But ever since that touch, as we are seeing on the screen right now,
no single part of her body is dislocated and she is doing things, that she could never do before.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sister, you said before that you couldn't even write.
Could you just, for the glory of God, demonstrate what you can now do,
just to testify to the people of God the wonderful healing in your life.
So we can see our sister there; she is actually writing on a board.
Nthabeleng Ramoedi & Family
Healing Testimony
Thank You, Jesus!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
You mean to say, sister, you couldn't do this before?
It would look like a cat's scratch, trust me.
You wouldn't know if the "G" was an "O" or whether the "D" was cojoined to the "O", or something like that.
Wow. Thank You, Jesus Christ!
Now, for the glory of God; we just want to see you walking freely in the midst of the people of God,
to demonstrate what you can now do that you couldn't do before,
or if you attempted to do it before, a part of your body would dislocate.
Wow, we can see our sister walking freely, in the midst of the people of God.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
You said, sister, that before, you couldn't even stand up straight, like you are standing now.
No, I couldn't stand up straight.
I would always - I had a hunchback.
But now I'm all straight up.
I could even try modelling, if I wanted to.
My posture is all back now.
Wow, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Indeed, the evidence of Jesus Christ is lives changed.
Our sister knows the extent of the differences in her life after that prayer.
For her entire life, she has been in pain and that has been her normal life.
She has been accustomed to pain, to different parts of her body dislocating at any given time.
But right now, we can see her standing freely in the midst of the people of God.
Sister, you said before you couldn't even talk like this to people for such a long time.
True, because in-between I would probably gasp for air like, "Hold on", then come back to you.
Or my eyes would start rolling because I had seizures as well,
or I would have to sit down for a bit, and I would never stand this long, without needing a chair,
which is actually very new for me.
Usually I would just pass lines; I would never queue.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
This is an incredible miracle and we give all the glory to God.
Sister, before listening to your advice, we would like to hear from our brother here as well
who has one or two words to say concerning the miraculous healing in your life.
Nthabeleng Ramoedi & Family
Healing Testimony
We are from Lesotho, and we are managing a private hospital that God Almighty offered unto us.
When medicine calls a diagnosis a syndrome, you should know we really are not sure of what is happening.
This young lady is my niece and we encountered the first, very severe symptoms of her disease in 2010.
She had just visited us and she developed this seizure.
I would say that was the most severe one that she had,
because we knew that from time to time she used to dislocate diverse joints in her body.
With this type of seizure she had, we gave her all medications that we knew,
that were supposed to abort her seizures but they couldn't help.
We had to refer her to a more equipped hospital, where she could meet a neurologist.
All diverse investigations have been done of her condition.
In this particular case, an EEG was done in order to conclude whether she was an epileptic
but all without a conclusive test.
Her heart muscles from time to time would be weak, her lungs would be weak, she would be on nebulizers,
she has had heart ECGs done several times, but all with normal results.
In short: she has been through all different tests, but it came out without any conclusive diagnosis.
Definitely, if muscles are not well, it means every organ can never function,
because we all are made of muscles and ligaments.
That is why her body could not control anything of her own.
But on top of all, I just praise God; I thank God for the healing that she received
because ever since last week I have been with her day and night
and she has never had what she had before we came here.
And I just thank God for that.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Madam, speaking from a medical perspective; what can you just testify about what happened
when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for her and those changes that you've seen in her body since then?
What can you say as a medical doctor concerning this?
When Prophet T.B. Joshua came to meet her, I personally knew that the devil was going to give up.
I am a living testimony because I had a lumbar spondylosis, for which I was prayed for,
and here I am standing.
What she went through was a major seizure, that every organ in her body just refused
and was arrested by the Spirit of God that was facing her.
At the end of it all, she was freed.
Immediately after the prayer, she asked to go to the toilet, and she was virtually running in front of me.
Being a very jovial person, she started dancing for everybody.
She has been perfectly normal, she has been eating normally,
she has never had the abdominal blow that she would normally have
and none of her joints has ever popped out.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
We give all the glory to God.
We just would like to ask you, madam: What is your word of advice, especially as a medical personnel,
what would be your word of advice and encouragement to our viewers all over the world,
and those who may be suffering from such an unusual disease; one that medically has no cure -
what is your word of advice to them?
Doctors, medical personnel, God uses us to treat but He is the only One who can heal.
When you are faced with conditions that are beyond our own understanding,
that is the time when we have to say, "God should take over".
We don't need to rely upon our own strength, or knowledge
because indeed, we are limited as human beings
and we have to be counsellors of our own patients, for them to know that God has the final say.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We really thank God for the role that our mother and father played in encouraging our sister to come
to The SCOAN, and taking care of her to the point where she received that prayer.
We would like to hear a word from our father here as well.
Sir, you are welcome.
Please, introduce yourself to us and tell us what you can say about the wonderful healing
in the life of our sister here.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Indeed, God is with us.
Of course, if God is with us, who can be against you?
No one.
The patient has said it all.
I'm using the word "patient" because I'm used to that word.
Nthabeleng Ramoedi & Family
Healing Testimony
I'm from Lesotho.
We have a private hospital, God has blessed us with,
where we first saw the problem of epileptic seizures, which really were not epileptic.
On my left side is my wife; we have been married for over 30 years, and we thank God for that.
The young lady is the niece.
They have said everything about the condition.
You see, every organ in the body has a collagen fibre, or muscular tissue.
If you have a problem in the brain, obviously it may result in a fit.
For you to have multiple conditions in the intestines, joins, jaws of any kind,
then it is a confusion that people would treat in isolation.
If you have an eye problem, it is treated in isolation,
if you have an intestine problem, it is treated in isolation,
if you have a bladder issue, it is treated in isolation.
It is almost impossible to have all these conditions under one's eye, except the eyes of God.
So, we decided to bring her to The SCOAN, where we have received deliverance and healing.
My wife is a living testimony; she had spondylosis and disc prolapse, and here she is standing.
There was no reason for us to doubt God.
In fact, I would want to say that in this world today, we have science, medicine, and organizations;
those are the things we believe in,
without realizing that it is God who has used people to create this science and medicine.
We should realise that when we fall out of rope, we should hang on to faith.
That is the very reason why we know that doctors fall sick as well.
If doctors knew everything, doctors would never be sick.
If scientists knew everything, the scientists would never be sick.
We all do false things, because we are natural, human beings.
We must turn to the supernatural, and that is the King of kings and the Lord of lords.
We thank God for the miracle.
The storm is over - thank God!
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sir, what can you testify about the changes in the life of your niece after the prayer,
and what can you say about what happened
when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for her on that day last week.
Yes; just before that, her shoulder dislocated and I had to push it back.
While she was sitting down, the knee came out of the position and I was trying to put it back,
and T.B. Joshua was praying for a lady just next to her.
Then Prophet T.B. Joshua came and as spoken to by Jesus, he was used to pray for the young lady
and all of a sudden she was on the floor.
Just a stretch of the arm again and everything, the storm in her life calmed down.
Since then, she has never had any dislocation from any single, big or small joint.
Neither has she had any convulsion or seizure.
She is fine, she is able to eat, she doesn't have any issues with her intestines.
She has actually had a constipation, which she had for 3 months before,
but now she doesn't have any condition like that.
She is fine and free - free at last!
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
And we know, as you rightly said, sir, that medically, this condition was incurable,
there was nothing that could be done more than had been attempted from a medical perspective.
But today, she is a living testimony to the glory of God.
What is your word of advice, sir, to our viewers around the world, especially those in the medical field?
My dear brethren in the medical and scientific field:
I would want to say that we are material beings and God uses us - it is good.
God has used us, God is still using us and God will use us.
Science and medicine are created by God;
therefore, we should know our limits and we should not be oblivious or boastful
when we take care of a patient and the patient gets fine.
We should know our limits and we should give credit to God, because we treat but God is the Healer.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
Finally, we just want to hear the last word from our sister.
We would like to hear from you, sister; what is your own word of advice to our viewers all over the world?
You are a living testimony to the power of God, and healing you've received.
What is your word of encouragement and advice to our viewers?
Never, never lose faith.
It doesn't matter how big your trial or situation is; don't let your situation determine who you are,
because God's time is always the best.
If someone told me 10 years ago, or 2 weeks ago that I would be here standing,
talking to all of you without any pain, I would have probably said, "Ha ha ha".
But with God's grace, I'm here and I'm not sarcastically laughing; I'm laughing because I'm happy.
I'm smiling for the first time without having any pain, I'm overjoyed.
Quite frankly, after the service, I will ask whoever is around, "Let's go dancing and praise the Lord".
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We can see this sling that your aunt is holding.
You said that this was something before you had to carry with you anywhere you went
because at any given time, a part of your body would dislocate.
What do you want to do with this now?
Let's just shove it off somewhere.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Brethren, we have listened to our sister's testimony.
Just imagine if God Almighty could heal her from a condition that had plagued her entire life,
causing extreme pain 24/7, today she is walking freely, living freely without pain to the glory of God,
what is your own situation?
Just use your faith to put a demand on the anointing that is available here,
and the same God that healed our sister is present to touch your own case today,
and your case will not escape the anointing of God, in Jesus' name.
If you believe that, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
TT ROBERT BEGIER 22/08/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 31/08/2018